we have seen some aspects of VL iw now
let's discuss the alive backward
compatibility as a quiz let's say we
have a simple viola W processor it has a
64 bit that specifies two operations so
it's roughly equivalent to two normal
instructions and let's say that this
processor fetches the codes and executes
etc one of these 64-bit instructions per
cycle now we want to build a better
version of this processor it can do four
operations per cycle so it will need to
fetch the code and execute two of those
64-bit instructions per cycle the
question for you is is this new
processor a viola W processor the
possible answers for you are yes it is
or no it's not really a viola double
processor